And you tell me the way to frame Everest
about two miles to the first main
intersection and then turn left it's about
sixty miles thanks but Town of this
suddenly suddenly one no no that's
the name that's a funny name for
a town. Hang over from the old days
that the way things used to happen here
suddenly I wrote agents gamblers gunfighters
Well I get things to change. Things
happen so slow now the town council has
begun to change the name to gradually that
I thank God that pleasure
come back. Will remove
the old. The
old the the.
Old.
Or with the the. The way.
The small.
Old.
Hello there bridge. Where is your mother
we've been shopping i gotta accept look
out once I'm. Sure. Not.
Well no I guess not she would
make me who she was of course
well you better say Mom it's kind of not
polite to say she like that especially
about your mother well anyway she wouldn't
you know I but I guess what's on your
mind. Well now let's see you
want an ice cream soda not
a bad idea but that's not if you want to
go to the movies started to wipe your mama
let me see why pitch
a. Boy oh boy this is tougher and I
thought. I got it you want that baseball
bat well but you're all
for one. Is that it
here is not only the beauty but
sure it's no use mom when.
She does I know it's because of my father
being killed in the war. Look bad if
you have a God what would you do with
a stick about filling station stick about
the distinction. When kids are learning
to read just like you. Write about Burma
Well I think we can talk her into it why
would you want to be a peace
officer and all we got was
a bank monster mother doing
groceries. Let's go.
Oh I've got it thanks
Todd Hello I can I get
a lift of the house
Thanks anyway but I have
a car with me going to church
tomorrow did I think about
a quarter to eleven or. You never get her.
Well and I know you still believe me I
do and I'm trying to understand but I haven't
asked you to and. That's because I'm
in love with. You you
should. Why not as true
don't turn to. Ellen you can't go on being
a would over ever been over three years
and be done. Don't you understand no one
can take you to play I'm not trying
to take the place and try to make
a place of my own You've been wonderful
Totten and I'm grateful really I am but. I
can't see you. Ellen you've got to stop
doing this to yourself because you're doing
it to page two as well
as to me you're digging
a big black pit and shoving
all of us down into it may be
a long time. Pitch Where
did you get the gun
I bought it for and I was. Taught how quick
we fight you when my mom says I'm going
to be
a sheriff just by time take it off ph I
can't help it Todd you know I can't stand
seeing him play with
a gun but the boys gotta learn sometime the
guns aren't necessarily bad depends on
who YEARS OF THEM time cures one doesn't
think. Yes Well then just take it off page
. That's three dollars Great.
Thank you. L.O.L.
. I know you know of the boys as
a war pictures but as they mention children
you know death and destruction the
cruelties the torture it's got to know these
things exist then he can fight against
them one of his term can wrap the boy and
suffering we can try as long as possible
but what house is on fire everybody has to
help put it out because the next time it
might be your time to.
Search tomorrow I'm. So tired
I can't go in where I go on
a river I mean.
Or. Or or.
A bus going over to Philly for a cup
of java you can handle things with
a quiet quiet they had
a laugh with David. Gillick.
Good night Sure but the word get out and
he got the sheriff on the hill he had bad
but I'm urgently going. On and.
Will. Make it
a family twenty five. I'll be living under
a chair for the office and say what is
the. First time that your friend these
purchases and not discuss the event away.
From him alive and will eventually make
money out. Of interest in the.
News. To
a. Movie
.
That is for wait a second I
want to know what it is about
a top secret get out of here puppy
say get out of my pants off. Shut.
What the word lesson of the I am finished
typing to get sheriff Todd Shaw suddenly
California confidential cold angle. Special
train number ten nineteen carrying the
president of the United States well I arrive
suddenly five pm today President will
detrain and drive to White Springs ranch
will require adequate transportation
appreciate cooperation your staff with
secret service operators arriving one team
County acting chief U.S.
Secrets. No mistakes and only typing.
In the usual. State police headquarters
whether the cycle where again
hang on hang on. I love the Top Shot
on the Suddenly I want to get America.
Number twenty six to sixty. Seven
is top job say like I got to jail
because word is hang over now I'm going
to need five of your cars two men to
a car and one times I'm going to wage
a car and you. While. X.
. Got the same message there is
a show on the road already she does think
cops don't fool around to that they don't
say. It was billeted you said
confidential. Bunch of people that were
already out of your eyes the fact that.
I know you have the right sort of is no I
want the big black Cadillac aboard thirty
limousine part of the station back then.
I'm going to getting married if you don't
be funny this is Billy's business don't
tell anyone I don't get it you're not
supposed to or thirty M.
No slip ups.
Mr Carney right my name Shaw and I
think. What message passing over.
And I see your credentials.
I got a. Job in Cali I had to make You're
a great guy I got the
message. You know I have
a man show not all of this seems like a
good time to be the. We always have to be
a I'd be your credentials. If. I got
a limousine order for thirty it'll be parked
right here good state police have five
cars on the road and weather me excellent
good that's about it not quite you can
still be of help that was. We'll have to
check all those stores basing the station
Mr Carney I know every pride in this town
you can take my word for I can take your
word for anything I'm
sure they're OK it's just
a piece I bought. Way back
a limousine between the practice and if I
shall rise pretty rough in there maybe
easier to cover I'll state police cars
going there to. Live up there in the
hills Bob Benson is grandson and his
daughter in law we'll check it out
Mr Carney if there's one place in this
town doesn't need check in is that one pop
Benson used to be in the Secret
Service themselves for bad take
a retarded pop Benz. You don't
mean Peter Benchley. Well.
What do you mean. Pete Bensen
used to be modeled. Like that
therefore Mr Shaw he'll be
the last one in the world.
Probably
a rectifier probably too would you please
call just in having come up and think
that thing before you record right.
Now have you want to stand I've built
a television transmitter in thirty eight
before you even know what television was
but didn't work I don't know I never did
get to finish the receiver but this is
a receiver and I do wish you'd call just I
don't want to bother the other side this
time and
a half on Saturday will not be cheaper
than what it will cost when you get to
diddling with it Alan stop saying
I may just go if you want God had
a fire. You haven't touched your
kid one. Since darling I mean
it especially for you you made because
you wouldn't let me or my god. Think You
Know Me saying well that's what the
guys only. Well I don't care what they
call you on your mother and I think
I know what's best for you. Pinch.
Pete you should be talking to you
that you are finished the boy just as
a point of that's all Alan. Please stop
interfering. Voice to cast blame on the
high court. And the next thing go
to your room have a program in
a setting and we want to. I've had this
for the last time Ellen you're going up
girl you got
a problem you haven't worked that's no
reason why paid to have your problem I've
only done what I thought was right. I read
about an experiment once kept germs away
from
a kid raising pure unscientifically. First
time I got on the run the court called
not an ammonia What does that have to do
with Paige because I hadn't been exposed
to have known unity of cruelty and they
didn't tyranny in the world you can't make
believe they aren't there and this is going
to learn what is the law and what is in
the law so they can defend the
defendant so he can become
a soldier and go out and be murdered like
his father was. And my son was killed in
a performance over studio duty being
blown to bits on some god but taken
battlefield thousands of miles from where
he was born you call that duty Yes I love
that would you like the page would that
make you happy Pete could hear you know I
think he'd be ashamed of you can you see
a terrible scene like. The old boy's wrote
those words life liberty and the pursuit
of happiness he sounded mighty
nice but they wouldn't open with
a plug nickel if somebody got made
a mistake. The way. Yes
. The AG Now who.
Knew. You. Couldn't find.
But with the surprise of the last sirens
blasting I'm trying to be. To put.
That thought. Wearily or to roost
in the way Springs right you
can go around here down main highway one
is the rivers and the ranch is about part
of my. Question is what was. It is
a rough life in those stores to decide
to change. Mr Carney raver Pryor in this
town has been here at least five years I
know that when other kids share the stage
or that my view is one of those
stories are covered like the leg of
a tennis defied stay locked up. But
on the road to. Getting the word
No I'm including the proprietors I don't
remember the Stars like that and I was
inside after ten minutes if
I might be shot aside like
a man it's important yesterday. That we're
going to get the station Kelso take over
Troopers a lot of credit approaches one
for the right and then another has
a house on the no. No I'll
check that one myself.
Saw Davies is going on the spur to talk a
little maybe uranium strike not exactly
a look slim take over here and I'll catch
up with you later four thirty on I want
all the dust Geographic at the Main Street
between Hogan all or the state boys will
help you if anybody in town squawks why
you smooth things over they know you and
this is all going to seem
a little strange that I'm confused myself
never have seen so many cops what goes on
. This is Mr Carney special agent the
Treasury Department Secret Service kerning
slim Adams one of my deputies How did you
secret service I get it they're shipping
the national debt through here in gold bars.
Just don't worry about it you'll find
out later like about the car you were.
Not well then you better put that got
away for your mom sees it saying I.
Did I Do we should call
a judge and I didn't come up and fix that
shot so I know will blow the whole day
passes I don't want pitch to miss the
ball game after missing the movie and
everything already going along get
ready to talk to say they will hold
a school down see what happens OK Do you
sure you know what you are doing Alan
please wish this on the back at this in
five thousand votes that's dangerous Ellen
will you please stop being
a woman when they both love you and thank
. You said that you were right I guess I'm
all right it's because you care enough
and some of me that's well. I
guess maybe about it called. I
was close to although it. Might have to
post enough to tell you what I would
probably think Gavin don't you cross the
room that is unless you were standing in
a puddle of water and then you'd be grounded
and if you were grounded it gives you
a dead are not darning where it
hurt like blazes you say wait
a minute said no stay away from those wall
plugs don't monkey with electricity and
once you know what you're doing why did you
grandpa you got me there boy. I'll get
it just as you'll be up in
a little while I'm sorry
hon it's like. This is
Benson This is your husband at home. No I
don't what I should have asked was Are
you the owner of this house no I'm not
blind to my father. I'm John Band Special
Agent Federal Bureau of Investigation my
man do you suppose I could have been.
Just
a. Bad. Oh I against
John Van special agents.
For heaven's sake F.B.I.
They weaken it why sure sure come right
Angeline and make it over home thanks not
at all I get quite
a kick out of this used to be with the
treasure to buy myself really back in the
old days collective Internal
Revenue tax collector and an L.A.
Secret Service don't say Greg was president
could use bodyguard you don't say you
have back and I gained twenty eight youngest
retirement in the service economy high
not heart trouble you understand an accident
I want to count special interest one
hundred that the slug right here that's
a nasty one how come you're still alive I
don't know large in my heart. To take it
easy to live or die in me you're lucky like
you still if it hadn't hit me I'm going
to be in the Secret Service some day but
he was going to be Sheriff like scores
like you were supposed to grow up to be
president names page Mr back led me to page
I know it's quite Mr Barron what did you
want to see is about is something wrong
nothing wrong yet Mrs Benson but there might
be we just checking on us on the House
the minute we have a look around help
yourself but I want to know and have
a look around with or without your permission
Mr Benson it's an emergency check.
They must be something the matter anyone
else live here beside you three know.
Anyone going by here today no just the usual
routinely Harris let them out which is
all about just being careful I'll
explain later. Two bedrooms one
bathroom all clear one
here just like they said.
The kitchen back Mantri back doors there's
good on the other garage on the kitchen
cellar door an all clear on
the garage. This for us said.
I'm sorry folks but I'm afraid we're
going to have to hang around for
a while why deal on this nothing of
course or something wrong the F.B.I.
Doesn't pay as of as back about well I
won't stay I'll take no man nobody leaves
the house until we do I know what happened
let's just go about your business like
with any other set of the afternoon
read your papers look at your T.V.
Anything you want nobody needs
to have something fishy about
all this official business what
sort of official Mr Benson is
a former agent of the Secret Service you
should understand you know I'm getting all
still but I'll sign at five pm this afternoon
the president of the United States
arrives in town on
a special watch. And.
Then you mean to say the
person is going to get off the train that's
right. The president was the greatest
thing ever happened to this
town I'm. Sorry kid you know
Betty bring in the gear for the car back
but you see the back door is locked tight
and check this out of to be sure. I
still don't understand Mr Benson
it should be obvious to you that if anybody
wanted to kill the president we could
do
a beautiful job of it right in this window
of us with the love of Mike may be true
but you don't think that only me cos not
we have to remain here to protect you and
the president from somebody
else who might call.
Yeah. This all routine seems to me to be
kind of overboard I mean all this checking
and everything is all you expect in this
town. Have you noticed any strangers in
town during that I. Know you're sure sure
I'm sure I know everybody in this burg
only strangers we get our tourists you
know we get them all the time stopping for
gas by D.
That's all we want to know from either you
or your deputies the minute anything to
doesn't keep going through. Then this
isn't routine No it is. Can you tell me
the Los Angeles police picked up
a small time stupid the night before last
chapter of a long life or death while
a better they probably died he told them
something was that what do you mean
something was up and about punishment.
Can you believe that in our business we
can't afford not to I mean a tip of
a dime stool pigeon still even very proud
of being an American before he goes.
Crime is crime but this is something
else again right so we can begin to. Go.
Crazy depending. On when you know ph we
have to stay here you can watch him for me
but I want to get well you just tell us
go boy bring him right up the. Sorry page
so that after
a lot about the phone in the kitchen let
me ask if we don't change the pattern
it'll give Benny.
Something I don't understand I was in the
service myself so you told me that we
made every question we check we never
went to extremes like this unless unless
you're with that that there
was to be in the census as
a nation you don't mean I
mean it. But your F.B.I.
Secret Service is responsible for the safety
of the president well using everybody
this to Mr Benson I look down that.
State troopers local law enforcement
agencies and. You know
a voting Carney's done I had you know I
worked together in the old days. With the
presidential staff now it's
confidential information. This is
a terrible thing. That's your image that's
just my way I'm an American and I saw
everybody is what we. Are something. That.
He she has been someone with.
I don't know I think. Was on
the low right. With at Notre Dame Connie
great well I'm sure it ran in the face of
that. Friend of yours in
your video diaries and then
Karl it's great to see. All but just like
me live wherever they are guy you get
involved just what do you expect after
twenty five years I want to ensure I want to
make yourself at home my daughter and my
grandson pay just let the kind of secret
service he got the president by Mr Barron.
Man Oh you don't know you've always got
here ahead of me.
One sound from the kid and he dead.
Train muscle that. We're going
to sell or give and take
the rough with it to get away.
You get the message brain boy.
I'm going to be still no noise.
That's you want to hate Let's go.
Now it's over with you
you're all busted up.
All right. Take care. You've
got it now let's be practical.
I don't want any more shooting around you
I want to be nice and quiet and cozy I
get a ring around and explain the weather
one phony and she's got a kid with
a stroke cut doesn't make much noise
that way. Same goes for you to
anybody steps on the line
the boy. That simple.
I love listening Ellen pay attention now
listen to me I don't look like that
everybody is all right you've got to get
a hold of yourself no matter what happens
you've got to hang on if you scream or
make one false move will murder the
boy you understand your murder page.
Here I'm lazy. You are right
all right inside with
a long time to wait like. For the
kitchen table in front of the window.
All right sit down sit down let your T.V.
Network know what came over that takes
so much time so that when a boy or
a clock keep yourself
occupied I got to think.
How do you thank you very well know
that the bone broken I guess he's bled
a lot we need
a doctor look at these thank you. Telepath
you know Dr Allan we can't have no
doctor we can't get
a broken arm. Off your new
me greatness practice
you couldn't take it you
straight. Hold on brave boy.
Tied up. He take him
into the bedroom sure.
The boy stays here.
And leaves the door open.
All right let's go to work.
We've got to do something I know I don't
want want. None of us tell but even page
you can catch long as we're alive
we got a chance we got to find
a flaw in his plan we'll think of
something. Haven't you going to. Come.
Do my good.
It's
a load. I had to cut you some
kind of page. Yeah. Leave
me alone Benny do you know what he said he
said it was going to too much television
in
a bad scored just tell him to
shut up. The things metals are
still tough chrome legs. I think it would
the difference is the brackets go into
the leg and under the floor with
a table and dance. And
you're getting too fresh so
Budmouth Johnny while the
trouble big deal listen
a lot of work do it that way but Johnny
I don't do it Benny. I want to get
a gun I got a solid base you see
when we get to it guns got to have
a record on stand still. We got
just three seconds to mail
a present. I want the table to show me
when we get. Tommy gun to do just as
good
a gun stinks now accuracy no punch my
lawyers are out of. This is that gun.
When I was in the army so I
was in the Army. About five
cars just not yet this is quite a
gun Benny Hill had a gun I did
a lot of chap in in the
war with a baby like this
a lot of chop. You're wrong
about me page you have
a coward. For I got to sell the
stock. At the casino talking to
resistance. I killed twenty seven men
all by myself. I want to sell the Star
medal. So I.
During periods they can take
lessons should I take it
a day. Johnny rely X.-O.
FOR THE LOVE OF MY what the
silver star I want it. To Johnny
K.
You want it. I
got him. In there
a long time. Yeah get
him back in here. When
y'all trying to pull. All the inside.
Come on come on. Feeling better
Yeah you're lucky you may know when
you're meant to blow your brains out it's
a bad show yeah but I'm not so maybe you
better sit down and stay there and we'll
be safe with everybody you've got to do the
look in your eye I seen it on the line
a line you have an annoyance
some of the time down.
By your pool I was up front put in the
grass quick. To think of everything.
Great is great fun is well
advertised. It's close I'm.
Happy here.
With time it is. All right suppose you
tell me what happened in this house on the
side of the at the NO between
four and five. Smart guy.
Sure we don't break that
pattern we're here for
a reason and if we break it we might blow
the deal you know where you are slinging
the paper over the fence around four thirty
in. The livery boy if you come in. And
warehouse cyan on one of the mountain
jackrabbits you'll be miners way back when we
stop when you get down to
brag about anybody else not
a lot of anybody know that you on the other
guy were coming up to. An interesting
question what's the interesting
answer you guess telling Tom.
Sheriff if you think I have any qualms about
killing this kid you couldn't be more
wrong. The thing about killing him where
you are on him is that I wouldn't get paid
for it. And I don't like
giving anything away for free.
Including information. You've got to show
all over the place brave boy. Not me
I'm scared you see the way I figure I'm
a dead man anyway so the
boy saw the SOS pop just
a question an hour later
and I give the president
a bit of an edge why don't we get it now
they will care if they won't hurt Peachy
said Joe because it's convenient album
you think these crimes would kill the
president and then take off leaving us
behind to identify low he said you wouldn't
take pitch Sure sure and I meant it don't
listen to this guy he's just been great
with your kids life I know guys
like that in the army we just want
a job that's all identifying us is not about
by seven o'clock tonight we'll be out
of the country and you'll never see us
again telling time telling never mind lady
we'll just assume that they knew we was
coming up here so that somebody else comes
up to check on and you can tell on the
sheriff and his friend were here but they
had to go someplace else that's
all I have to go back to.
I go with my. I knew how come.
OK table screwed down all right
because I thought of things
a little and it's like bullets
right by the table put
a sentence out of the window. I thought
I told you this just stretching my legs
you're
a very careful man. That's right plan on
everything I'm sure if the first man issued
to them on Iraq I'll take pains to assess
never been done before and that is this
was my worry. I got time away I just make
my plans and carry them out that's what
John Wilkes Booth ought to do.
I know actor busted my leg on
a stage so I can yell down
with a tyrant's it was a such
a hammy might have made it pretty far
that they'll go kill Garfield didn't make
a deal with him he didn't
plan anything just took
a lucky shot strictly left handed just like
McKinley and this anger I got that you
were is trying to Roosevelt he
had to try to crowd. Crowds
So nobody ever made it up to
here I'm just a guy making
a living and I think you start
smart enough as you were.
By to take over bennies with any Yeah
Johnny. Down time he was going on
down there especially the station plan
leave the car you know why me because we
like and fly
a plane and you can't tell me I'm
expendable No I just don't want anything to
happen and we were going to
take because of they nail you
a Benny We need the car to get to the playing
China the place is clear we have paid
a job. You can't say get
enough. I'll be back.
Johnny. I can study just
like you want to move
a role in. All over.
Over the good. For
where it's run. Big beautiful
booby trap where you
can't do this you can't do it. A
year on Friday. Take
a look. Around on the ground
where you were.
Told. A. I can't go but I'm going
to do. What you are an American
citizen. And one minute
after five I'm going to be
a very rich American citizen to let
me get away with it show that. The.
Ghettos that make it take a pill may be
the old man's reach a terrible thing
a narrow minded Ah well you're
just another man a man with
a president. Who has. Never
killed the President.
Whose ass and just Kelly television
set one on a blank I once had
a farm become infectious
with the word watch
a blog by just tell it well we simply
forgot that so is Imus boy band Alright I'm
OK but if you question yes he was
you won't. All right ha you got
a bar. In the bottom and watch it.
No. We have to keep this man talking.
I mean as much as we spend some early
breakfast. Find
a way to get. Better get you think
you're right before you like
a pretty good sales morning and. Tied
what happened to you. Same thing will
happen to you unless you do exactly as
you're told. You can is that real is
real right but you know just tell
me what are you doing. To fix
a television set. Surprised by case. I
don't have any don't that's what you want
what is this a stick up yeah that's it's
a stick up you'll never get away with The
Globe and so on Buster. Your luggage with
the. I don't take
it there on the bank with the gun far
that's gone on with your story Main Street
who runs it just me or
do you have to point
a gun at me alone answer him yeah like
that when you left nobody knows you're
coming here that's right just
a service call I come makes me
nervous Mr I'm not going to be
a hero you can put the gun away. But
I'm telling you Buster like the others
one pass and the kid gets
it. That's right he gets it
so you see his life depends
on you gotta step.
Back and know he's certainly been gone
a long time. Maybe
we got
a little the gun now to be sure. That's
just what the show would like to forget
about me I've had it. Don't con me the
minute this gun was loaded one of your brave
boys might decide to go for the ride just
to fire it and if you fight it might
a little few stakeouts down and the game
would be over when it is only for now of
course. I want to go by
but I want to bring me
a little glass of milk with you Johnny my
also made me just watch him by watching.
I don't think it would somebody
tell me would. Be quiet.
Any feelings i. Know I haven't lady
that was taken out of me by experts
feelings a trap. Show me a guy
was feeling and I'll show you
a sucker. So weakness makes you think
of something besides yourself.
I have the feelings left to me at all or
be for me. Just Me Do you ever think of
your mother your father think
of him. I used to think I'm
a great deal my mother was unmarried my
old man was
a dip so they left me in the home. Page
come back here. All the.
Nice go and buy so many capital
given too much though.
You know beat his brains out
a little but the funny. Thing you say I
kept this till I had let yourself second as
a pretty good Milo and I make every where
they don't say baseball is brains that. A
couple of big bad men get scared that by
a six bit capital I own that I'm not sure
they couldn't take you go up with the
milk and they're also bring me
a bit is that they. Need some milk paints
pretty bad when they want to hear from
Betty. I said.
If this mistake up what is this
did you come up here to fix
a television set you need when in fact
the television set. They're planning to
assassinate the president which presses the
president of the United States Iraq was
here this afternoon you're
kidding. No you're not kidding
the press killed the
President. They couldn't do
a thing like that and thinking traitor is
your Benedict Arnolds are you guys crazy
you can't do a thing like that reckless
Don't you realize what that means that's
a fascination if you're president to make
a deal with your boy we kill you instead
of the president that's even steven OK
with you. Not anybody else want to take the
heat of the president but your share of
a bad job. Anybody else want to volunteer
I can meet their enemy agents.
All right who is behind it. I haven't the
slightest idea at all then of are you
curious I'd shut up for the last I like
you Sheriff you got guts you must've been
a good soldier I got back I want to Silver
Star that's pretty good kill twenty
seven Gerry's all that myself You're
a born killer that's all you
know some guys like that I know
a couple. Just when you get real good to
somebody or murder. Or they cannot go
a whole platoon a guy
invents a bomb and kills
a hundred thousand people just like that
and the biggest moments here you put
a slow going to double crossing score that
isn't even worth very and you have to
think again I got no feeling
against the president just owning
a living by trees in
a store scraps give it up politics jazz
is not my right that I don't even always
Bamian I want to know what the difference
didn't occur to you or why they want you
to do it certainly it did but that makes
them stop it's not me I'm the guy I was
getting that made but since you
know if a man can stand for so much
a normal before the war I
didn't write always lost in
a great big crowd I hated that crowd I
used to dream about the crowd once in
a while I used to see all those faces
scratching and shopping and by and then the
mist would clear and somehow all those
faces would be me all me and all nothing
but the war changed everything
a bear and I'm no traitor
Sheriff I want to Silver Star
and learn how to kill
you know. Maybe I did.
Maybe that changed everything and the
people began to know I was after the
show I hoped up with an outfit for good
though the finger said where and how much
and Johnny bounded the job you think anybody
else could handle this job you think
better we'll look at the when I don't think
too much Johnny nobody else can do this
job because they got too much
feeling and feelings no good I got
nothing against the president
sheriff he just with a half
a million bucks to me tax free make
my own laws about the taxes to pot
the guy his school shut up just. Listen to
him Buster and don't ever say that again
and. You heard him just.
Several million dollars
And yeah. I thought
a scratch off and I could retire on I'm out
of scratch how do you know it will ever
be paid if it's been paid on the rest.
I'll get it I will be sure it's not
just the man the president that's what so
funny life is on the guise of paying the
freight always slow they don't even
know what they're doing a half
a million plans for absolutely nothing we
got tonight at five o'clock I kill the
president one second after five years
and the president what changes nothing
what are they paying for nothing
otherwise I wouldn't take in
a job you take on you
think so yeah it was.
Alright take it
a while and. Do it your soul and
everything be fine answer straight
clean and plain. Answer it.
Now. And yeah train's on
time the car will be waiting in front of
the station like your bigot facing you.
Get back as soon as you can
and don't be followed.
Oh.
As the big boys kind of. Lovely. Old Mr.
Get up there. What's your name Fred
but again what are you doing in
town just passing through Where's your
car I don't have one I second from Three
Rivers waiting for the train now
that I think the train on the L.A.
What train. Five o'clock the five o'clock
now that's right strange why I said
because we don't have any five o'clock
train the stops here Mr except today and
that happens to be
a special that you don't know
about except that you do. Must
be some mistake you made.
On I look after I I got
a benefit cation. I can prove who I am I
got my driver's license right here and.
Then I. The girl.
Yes.
Thank.
Ye. Thank you note.
I told you not to kill him not to kill
him after he was our only like come on.
So long Benny I think I'm the only
hope that I could and. We got him
down for just like one canid last checkpoint
I was on the Hill that's right in the
job protect the white man's right about to
have been able to reach them or take two
troopers and backtrack and start when I
was on the Hill we've got the fine card
right. Now we've got trouble
with everybody except Mrs
Benson down the cellar when I don't
know nothing I hope. Anybody gets
brave kill em all you can only hang once.
That step there. But. I look at
a grip on yourself I want you to look relaxed
if you don't pull it off everybody is
dead the understand all of us dead So be
yourself do what you me I'll come up here
to check whether kanina show up with you
and I want you to go out front I don't
want to man the house you know how or what
to say just go out in one of the flowers
do anything you like but
keep busy. Let's take
a roach quick. Listen to make castle
and. They'll come up to check whether
Connie and the sheriff with us suddenly
they were here they came up to check the
house but it's three o'clock they left
here when out on the White Springs ranch
Well it took pop and the kid with them and
that's the last you saw them you got it
. You got it. If you look like
a ghost. Pull it off lady or everybody and
everybody.
I mean you next but then again.
I don't thing in mind oh
shut up you guys. Mrs Benson.
My name's Haggerty so you must be one of
the CARNEY That's right is he been here.
He came up here about three o'clock to
check the house they said I don't know why
who is that why is the Carney in sharp
sharp and they said they had to check the
White Springs ranch road as your father
in law Mr Benson here well you know.
You see he used to be Mr Carney's chief
Yes I know actually Mr Carney took him
along my little pony too when
you're alone. And you haven't heard
from him since he left no no I haven't
something's wrong I know something's wrong
now now Mr Benson nothing's wrong we're
just talking that's all. But if you see or
hear from them before I do please have
them check the details on the railroad
station it's very important thank you
all right lady inside.
Very nice very nice job congratulations.
If you don't like me do you.
And I like you either animals kill each
other live that's what you do and they like
aerospace medium rare or well done.
All right Bob run
a minute clear. She
just you haven't got the guts.
And you can't. Take it
but remember the square in the cellar.
That's right. Think of the present for
us. Let's not think of ourselves.
I didn't give you I don't chance
but you don't even think I have
a chance. Of
doing OK Johnny sure everything's fine
you played a part real good should be
a delegate you are not going to fix the
television set you told me to set get your
stuff and fix it will keep you from getting
patriotic to stop the moment touch your
fix this that and shut your mouth I don't
like what you say anyway not fix it we
still got time. For
us.
Open up.
About two hundred yards Bernie is not
a German rival Yeah you know what I
know I'm where were you during the war
all the way from the kashering that I
want to Silver Star when you went to the
elbow whalebones you going to Germany
now. But you're one of those big guys now
with the gold on the shoulder I was
a corporal about you Corporal I'm
a sergeant you didn't like officers
offices big shots yes or no sir so let's.
Take shots you don't like big shots when
you are big and. I killed militaries and
any five officers put together I did some
pretty good chap in the war pretty good
like I said before you're
a born killer that's all. They taught me
how and I liked it. When I see you know
used to stay there and shake like
a leaf while I chop if more guys like me
have come anyone think there how come you
miss Germany they sent me home my toe is
finished your tour any infantry are you
kidding Well you've been issued during
the infantry when I plant you in
a box tour that was by the Air Corps turn
it off probably went over the hill I sat
down and you know Baron you got the yard
look you look Yardbird to me down in the
tunnel big shot with the Yardbirds Come
on now tell me where were your court
martial What was it for rape. Not killing
that's what you like killing babies
rooting down our B.W.
That's not shut up. But I
go you got away with it so
I got it Section eight you want out of
Section eight Section eight psycho in charge
of killing you know I knew guys like
you killing was sweet brother kill
a man and love a girl
a real kick that's real what they got coming
back stop it or maybe didn't like your
seal maybe
a shot in the back that
it maybe if you. Like I
said.
Going to keep it up shut.
Up. And I can keep kicking
as long as you keep you in your face off
and. You are right you blew the part to.
Have
a person in the second and I was thinking
Jack if you want to plant the main plague
late do a good ground like
that table here to get
a better picture let the lines and. Plant
the main played the lead to the table cut
the static one expert direct the
segmental to get out of Mexico.
That's right Jen all of these
is a high potential ground
a long way from abroad to the station
what do you guys get the technical talk
Western no radio my
advantages really are for
a while one might have been all right
it's not exactly sound but I was there
a scam
a while when the German police right all
right all right stopped the bullet and
fixed that in that way. So. That maybe.
It is right he has a bad
one by Pelosi brought
a bill I'm going to stay
put in the Kill get
a. Little
. Kids put down the gotta get
one if you're going. To send
me.
You know I think probably I Gotta Feeling
a heart attack to find and
but I'm one of the it's not
a force you better watch. Out either thank
you but thinking you'd like to take
a crack at this right I want to get myself
killed yes frankly Sheriff I don't think
you might get yourself killed. Nobody wants
to die so we have to talk about want to
shut up good. Talk is
a lie no no why would have. To get
myself because it's my mother's and
a shot might bring the stage will be
starting all over the joint before the
president arrives. If I can put you away
in two seconds by twisting your arm again
that weighs no knowing so I'll go when I
think most want to meddle. With joy when
in the post-mortem I'll anymore than you're
going to enjoy the money when you say
what you say I said nobody ever made
you won't either. You don't think
so. So you got
a plane you never read ahead of the police
and if you do you'll never make it to
the border you ever hear the jet fighter
you know how many air strips there are
between here and the border you know
a fellow could get an education just
listening to this guy but maybe he's right
Doug said have the money
had already been paid
a smart guy would hit the road right now
fly out of here at the present and spend
the money in South America. He's right
Johnny. Why take the risk we can land now
we can make it we don't have to forward
this thing to China something wrong with
that chicken chick All right I'll call
it chicken I want to be rich and dead.
Johnny the guy's right you've got to
lift a coffin get out of you have
a good one for
a cause and one of those scraps anyone can
check and they didn't waste any time on
him I think we haven't touched. It Off by.
Bashing me in front of the sheriff children
even if we swing it he's the president
of the giver and you don't figure the guys
are paying off we're just going to let
you fly away to you that you dislike the
Secret Service I thought of that to show
it might be an internationally embarrassing
situation if the feds happen to get up
with us first so Bart you just gotta realize
that everybody's going to be on your
tail from five o'clock in
the day you die there's
a hole in your argument what is it we're
already wanted from us so you can only
take the gas once again as
Johnny they won't get us by
not. Johnny leave that to me.
You're sick to make your sick I don't like
that don't play God Just because you've
got a gun but you see Sure that's
the way it is when you've got
a gun you are sort of God If you had
a gun I'd be the champ and you would be
the god. The gun gives you the power of
life and death. A funny sort of feeling to
have control of life and death you want
to have a drone or you could
miss a man if you had
a mind to or you could kill dead in its
tracks. That made you kind of God I liked.
Without the gun or nothing. And I never
had anything before I got my. First
time I got one of my hands and killed
a man I got some self respect. I was
somebody. Like this kid over here.
If that cap is that was a real gun and
I didn't have a gun he be a kind of
a god to and I wanted my life I worship
the ground he walks on and I pay and they
have
a million dollars in my life. To
do because life is all I had. At
this point doesn't have the gun I
have and I can lose the like me.
All right all night I'm fine I'm
fine I was so nice description.
But I was so much going like they were
going to have that kind of do you. Know it
was likely All right thank you so I kind
of. You're wrong about God and the gun
show. Without the gun you would never
suspect that me you would never be even
noticed. Because if they're gone you
will remember me as long as you live.
With them now going for the sixty six
crossing outside town all right nobody
knows this is it you're over there. And you
see once we're going to do it but this
is my meat we're going to do it.
For the return from. The if you.
Have the best.
The AS.
Yet. And.
The and.
Rare.
It didn't stop.
It didn't stop it.
No. Thought No three.
No it's. A little but.
Sure you're going to be all
right Mr Benson R.L.Y.
And I mean this is us now
they are right I don't need
a nice mate. For the grateful to you I'll
come to China right to the station so
they cancel the stop
of we're going to take
a chance on the president's safety once it
was pulled southward to our present one
on the Los Angeles that's the station I'm
afraid to stand by those guys are going
to stop taking you Ram I do as I was was
and I hope that thanks again Mr Benson
I'll do to you on that I'm not. Understanding
of the panic I just come from your
nonsense boy of about to be president
presidents have learning that I'm damn pop
and grandpa bank manager.
Or will.
Or will and. He didn't make it.
I'm playing critical but they didn't get
the all right. I guess somebody had to
make and. Was. Coming back
to this morning the prince.
Get in town driving home. The
length I've got to go to the opera.
Can I pick up an instrument.
The M.E.
Well
a low. Blow
.
Yes but you tell me the way the three rivers.
You get out of the first intersection
you turn left that the about sixty miles
banks want this town suddenly suddenly one
now that's the name. That's up on
a broad down. I don't know. I
don't know the blue.
Blue. Or red.